# **EMIL MADSEN**

emilmiliam@outlook.com • linkedin.com/in/emil-madsen-7400a6222/ • github.com/Nesstark

#### **ABOUT**

I am a 23-year-old studying Medialogy at Aalborg University in Copenhagen, where I am learning, among other things, how to manage IT projects, from analyzing societal issues to developing concrete solution proposals.

Through my work experience, I have developed my collaboration skills and learned to understand workplace dynamics in a large office. I can contribute with great adaptability and I easily settle into new tasks.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Aalborg University in Copenhagen**

Started August 2023

Medialogy

# Slotshaven Gymnasium

Graduation June 2020

Study programme: Mathmatics and Physics

Elective courses: Social Science B, Psychology C, Astronomy C

**SKILLS** 

Design and modeling tools: SketchUp, Revit, AutoCAD, Microsoft Office

**Programming:** HTML, CSS, C#, C++, Python

Data analysis and statistics: Excel

**EXPERIENCE** 

# Banedanmark, Studentassistant

Mar 2024 - Now

· Administrative work, often in SharePoint and other ad hoc.

# Snevagten A/S, Administrative Sales Assistant

Maj 2022 - Nov 2023

Assisting the sales team in the company with administrative tasks.

### School (Bramsnæsvigskolen), Substitute teacher

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

• Substitute teacher for grades 1 through 9.

### Kindergarden (Børnehuset Holbæk Have), Pedagogical assistant

Dec 2020 - Maj 2021

Full-time pedagogical assistant, with a focus on a single classroom.

# Kvickly, Sales assistant

Jun 2017 - Jan 2021

Sales assistant and closing manager.

#### **OTHER SKILLS**

Design: Lightroom, Photoshop,

Miscellaneous: Word, PowerPoint, Sharepoint, Windows

#### **PERSONAL**

#### Languages

Danish: Fluent (Native Language), English: High level

#### Certificates

Drivers license, Diploma

#### Free time

Often used on my hobbies, photography, computers and time with my family